# AL-KHIQMAH MANZILATUL MUKAROMAH

 $089699923850 \ | \ \underline{\text{https://www.linkedin.com/in/al-khiqmah-m-m-79b7052b8/}} \ | \ \underline{\text{https://its.id/m/ProtofolioKaryaTulis}} \ | \ \underline{\text{https://its.id/m/MySertifikat}}$ 

## **Self Description**



I am a third-semester Information Systems student with a strong enthusiasm for exploring and developing myself in the fields of scientific research, data science, data analysis, business, and programming. I actively contribute to various organizations and events, including serving as an athlete in UKM Penalaran, a sponsorship staff member at Nalarfest, and an intern as RTA staff in HMSI. Additionally, I have a talent for writing in both scientific and literary fields. While I am still honing my skills in the areas I am passionate about, including those related to Information Systems, I am determined to grow and enhance these abilities to their fullest potential.

#### **Education**

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember

Departemen Sistem Informasi S-1 Sistem Informasi Surabaya, Indonesia 2023

**SMA NEGERI 1 PORONG** 

Mathematic and Natural Science Major

Sidoarjo , Indonesia 2023

### **Work Project Experience**

- Team leader for the biology project assignment from school "Research Report on Planting Media in the Growth of Mung Beans" 2022/2023.
- Team leader for the practical assignment project from school and the preparation and processing of a biotechnology scientific paper "Cassava Tape" 2022/2023.
- Team leader for the practical assignment from school of creating a book for the English literature task titled "FIREFLIES IN ENGLISH LINGUISTICS & LITERATURE" 2022/2023.
- Team leader for the practical assignment from school in Civic Education (PPKN) for a scientific research paper titled "The Impact of Instagram Usage on 12th Grade Students of SMAN 1 PORONG" 2022/2023.
- Team leader in the NEF UGM Group Business Case Competition 2024.
- Team leader essay competition group at the essay competition Camabea Unsoed

#### **Organizational Experience**

#### **Class Organization 12 MIPA 2**

Sidoarjo, Indonesia

**Secretary Class** 

2022-2023

I had experience as a secretary when I was in grade 12 where I was in charge of class administration such as filling in the class journal every day before class and then reporting the recap to BK before the ets/eas, recap class attendance and report it to BK, and since I served in grade 12 I once got an assignment from BK to recap what student to do after School of Senior high school, I was assigned by BK to recap career interests after graduating from high school.

UKM Penalaran ITS

Athlete Nalar project

Maret, 2024-Present

The organization I am currently in is as an athlete of Nalar Project UKM Penalaran ITS. The task of the Nalar Project athlete are focused on following and making projects to be exhibited at Nalarfest. Nalarfest itself is a big event of ITS Reasoning UKM. For now I am also participating in several competitions and am carrying out the progress of the Nalar Project.

#### **RTA HMSI**

Surabaya, Indonesia

Intership Staff 2024- Present

- Pengawalan PKM
- Humas PKTI TD

### **Committee or Volunteer Experience**

#### Nalarfest Expert Staff Sponsorship

Surabaya, Indonesia June 2024- Present

Sponsorship staff have the responsibility of finding and contacting potential sponsors via WA or email, drafting sponsorship proposals, and negotiating until an agreement is reached. However, there are some companies, who want to come directly to make a presentation only after that the proposal can be approved, in addition to that as staff also report progress during work meetings.

#### Nalar Discuss Kestari

Surabaya, Indonesia

August 2024 – 1 September 2024

Kestari in this Nalar Discuss is as a moderator when the discussion event takes place.

## Strength and Weakness

- My strength is that I am always diligent, consistent, so I always try to do assignments within the given time limit. Apart from that, I can also work in a team and can direct the team to complete tasks in accordance with team goals. I am also the type of person who is able to adapt and is willing to develop in any field.
- My weakness is that I often forget, so to overcome this deficiency I usually take notes in notes and reminders on my cellphone calendar or on paper. Apart from that, in communicating, especially with many people, I am not fluent in handling this. I try to take part in events, webinars, etc. can train my communication.

## Championships/Awards/Exposure from other activities outside the organization

- Top 1 Student consecutively in MIPA 2 class from semesters 3-6 at SMAN 1 PORONG, 2021-2023
- **Second Best Student** for the odd semester in 11th grade MIPA 2 class, academic year 2021/2022 at SMAN 1 PORONG, 2021
- Top 1 Student in the MIPA major for the even semester of the 2022/2023 academic year at SMAN 1 PORONG.

- Silver Medalist in the Study Wars Competition for the Natural Sciences category (SMA level) in 2021
- **Appreciative Medalist** in the Indonesian Language Olympiad at the SMA level, organized by Insight Olimpiade in 2021
- Top 1000 Participant in the Insight Mathematics Competition in 2021
- **Selected Author** in the national short story writing competition themed "DREAMS," organized by PT BARA PUSTAKA GROUP in 2023
- **Performer** at the graduation ceremony of 128 Information Systems students at ITS in 2023
- Participant in the "Starting Programming with Python" bootcamp (2023)
- Participant in the "Intro to Data Analyst" bootcamp (2023)
- Participant in the "Pekil Talk Zerobase" event. (2023)
- Semifinalist in the Futurest Business Case Competition in 2024

### **Training History**

- LKMM Pra-TD IV FTEIC (2023)
- LKMM TD IV FTEIC (2024)
- LKMW TD (2023)
- PKTI TD (2023)
- PSB (2023)
- BIMITS LEADERSHIP TRAINING (2023)
- DIKLAT UKM PENALARAN (2023)

#### Skill

- Writing
- Excel
- Figma
- Canva
- Microsoft Word
- Leadership
- Communication
- Innovative